

Date of Birth: Birth Place:

07.07.1992 Belgrade, Serbia

CONTACT

jovanvuceljic@gmail.com Email: jovanvuceljic.github.io/portfolio/ Website: +381645066848 Phone:

Bogdana Žerajića 15, Belgrade Address: LinkedIn

jovan-vuceljic

INTERESTS

Problem solving User Experience Web and Mobile Applications Science and Technology

HOBBIES

Gaming Speedcubing Cycling

Jovan Vučeljić

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

Economic Technician - Degree. 2007 - 2011High school of Economics, Belgrade, Serbia.

Informatics - Withdrawn. 2011 - 2014University of Belgrade, Faculty of Mathematics

Web Programing - Current. 2014 - Present ICT College of Vocational Studies. Belgrade. Serbia.

EXPERIENCE

April 2018 – Present Development of website and Frontend Developer web application dashboard, VR-All-Art UI/UX

April 2018 – Present Web Developer Digital Mind d.o.o. Website maintenance, web support for VR activations, web controllers, simple apps

Nov 2018 - Nov 2019 Full Stack Developer GladniSmo.com

Platform development, UI/UX, database development and management

SKILLS

React.js, JavaScript, Node.js, Meteor.js, Git, MongoDB, SQL, PHP, HTML5, CSS3.

ABOUT ME

I am passionate about developing utilities that can help people irrespective of its age and capabilities. My areas of Experience. Web interest are User and Mobile Development. Love to spend my spare time in identifying the solutions of challenging problems. For me, programming is a way of thinking.